export default {
  id: 'grammar_word_6_1',
  name: '문법책 단어 (6-1 / 91자 / 뜻)',
  data: [
    { question: 'きちんと', answer: ['', '제대로'] },
    { question: '世話', answer: ['せわ', '돌보기, 보살피기'] },
    { question: '迎える', answer: ['むかえる', '맞이하다'] },
    { question: '滑る', answer: ['すべる', '미끄러지다, 활주하다'] },
    { question: 'やっと', answer: ['', '드디어, 겨우'] },
    { question: '突然', answer: ['とつぜん', '돌연히, 갑자기'] },
    { question: '意識', answer: ['いしき', '(무언가를 신경쓰는) 의식'] },
    { question: '作文', answer: ['さくぶん', '작문'] },
    { question: '単語', answer: ['たんご', '단어'] },
    { question: '地球', answer: ['ちきゅう', '지구'] },
    { question: '残る', answer: ['のこる', '남다'] },
    { question: '製品', answer: ['せいひん', '제품'] },
    { question: '裁判', answer: ['さいばん', '재판'] },
    { question: '無くなる', answer: ['なくなる', '없어지다'] },
    { question: 'ろうそく', answer: ['', '초, 양초'] },
    { question: 'やせる', answer: ['', '살빼다, 살빠지다'] },
    { question: '観光地', answer: ['かんこうち', '관광지'] },
    { question: 'アトラクション', answer: ['', '놀이기구'] },
    { question: 'はっきり', answer: ['', '뚜렷히, 분명히'] },
    { question: 'しっかり', answer: ['', '단단히, 확실히, 빈틈없이'] },
    { question: '芝生', answer: ['しばふ', '잔디'] },
    { question: '確かめる', answer: ['たしかめる', '확인하다'] },
    { question: '保存', answer: ['ほぞん', '보존, 저장'] },
    { question: 'ネズミ', answer: ['', '쥐'] },
    { question: '丁度', answer: ['ちょうど', '마침, 꼭'] },
    { question: '火事', answer: ['かじ', '화재'] },
    { question: '引く', answer: ['ひく', '(사전에서) 찾다'] },
    { question: '仕方ない', answer: ['しかたない', '어쩔 수 없다'] },
    { question: '作品', answer: ['さくひん', '작품'] },
    { question: 'すっかり', answer: ['', '완전히, 죄다'] },
    { question: '途中', answer: ['とちゅう', '도중'] },
    { question: '連れる', answer: ['つれる', '데리다, 동반하다'] },
    { question: 'どんどん', answer: ['', '자꾸자꾸, 속속'] },
    { question: '葉', answer: ['は', '잎'] },
    { question: '混乱', answer: ['こんらん', '혼란'] },
    { question: '消しゴム', answer: ['けしごむ', '고무 지우개'] },
    { question: '黒板消し', answer: ['こくばんけし', '칠판 지우개'] },
    { question: '貿易会社', answer: ['ぼうえきがいしゃ', '무역회사'] },
    { question: '床屋', answer: ['とこや', '이발소'] },
    { question: '美容院', answer: ['びよういん', '미용실'] },
    { question: '化粧', answer: ['けしょう', '화장'] },
    { question: '許す', answer: ['ゆるす', '용서하다'] },
    { question: '特急', answer: ['とっきゅう', '특급'] },
    { question: '情報', answer: ['じょうほう', '정보'] },
    { question: 'できるだけ', answer: ['', '되도록, 가능한 한'] },
    { question: '電池', answer: ['でんち', '전지'] },
    { question: '負ける', answer: ['まける', '지다, (가격을) 깎아 주다'] },
    { question: '暖房', answer: ['だんぼう', '난방'] },
    { question: '一般化', answer: ['いっぱんか', '일반화'] },
    { question: '電報', answer: ['でんぽう', '전보'] },
    { question: '葬式', answer: ['そうしき', '장례식'] },
    { question: '座布団', answer: ['ざぶとん', '방석'] },
    { question: '新幹線', answer: ['しんかんせん', '신칸센'] },
    { question: '優勝', answer: ['ゆうしょう', '우승'] },
    { question: '経済', answer: ['けいざい', '경제'] },
    { question: '学科', answer: ['がっか', '학과'] },
    { question: '何度も', answer: ['なんども', '몇 번이나'] },
    { question: '構う', answer: ['かまう', '상관하다'] },
    { question: '喉元', answer: ['のどもと', '목구멍, 목 얹저리'] },
    { question: '絹', answer: ['きぬ', '비단'] },
    { question: '是非', answer: ['ぜひ', '꼭'] },
    { question: '鬼', answer: ['おに', '도깨비, 귀신'] },
    { question: '寿司', answer: ['すし', '초밥'] },
    { question: '締め切り', answer: ['しめきり', '마감'] },
    { question: '留守', answer: ['るす', '부재중'] },
    { question: '教授', answer: ['きょうじゅ', '교수'] },
    { question: '分野', answer: ['ぶんや', '분야'] },
    { question: '暖房', answer: ['だんぼう', '난방'] },
    { question: '港', answer: ['みなと', '항구'] },
    { question: '台所', answer: ['だいどころ', '부엌'] },
    { question: '失礼', answer: ['しつれい', '실례'] },
    { question: '絶対に', answer: ['ぜったいに', '절대로'] },
    { question: '多分', answer: ['たぶん', '아마, 아마도'] },
    { question: '水道', answer: ['すいどう', '수도'] },
    { question: '考え方', answer: ['かんがえかた', '사고방식'] },
    { question: '普通', answer: ['ふつう', '보통'] },
    { question: '滑る', answer: ['すべる', '미끄러지다'] },
    { question: '割合', answer: ['わりあい', '비교적으로'] },
    { question: '字引', answer: ['じびき', '사전, 옥편'] },
    { question: 'ほとんど', answer: ['', '대부분, 거의'] },
    { question: '花見', answer: ['はなみ', '꽃구경'] },
    { question: '専攻', answer: ['せんこう', '전공'] },
    { question: '代わりに', answer: ['かわりに', '대신에'] },
    { question: '棒', answer: ['ぼう', '막대, 봉'] },
    { question: '録音', answer: ['ろくおん', '녹음'] },
    { question: '機能', answer: ['きのう', '기능'] },
    { question: '領収書', answer: ['りょうしゅうしょ', '영수증'] },
    { question: '総理', answer: ['そうり', '총리'] },
    { question: '大統領', answer: ['だいとうりょう', '대통령'] },
    { question: '方法', answer: ['ほうほう', '방법'] },
    { question: '担当者', answer: ['たんとうしゃ', '담당자'] }
  ]
}
